Who's the king? I'm the king!
谁是王  我是王
What's new kid doing?
新来的这孩子在干什么呢
- What the...? - I command you to reveal your true form.
-你干...  -我命令你显露出你的真实
- Do you wanna die, buttsnack? - What is a "Buttsnack"?
-你想死吗  臭小子  -臭小子是什么
Hey! No fair!
这不公平
Just stay still and get pummeled.
不要动  乖乖挨揍
Hey! Cut it out, kids!
住手  孩子们
Oh! I can't not watch!
我看不下去了
Ha! Knock him back to wherever he came from, Steve!
把他打回他的老家  史蒂夫
Delete your mouth, Seamus.
闭上你的嘴  西莫斯
Keep still, so I can punch your face!
别动  让我揍你的脸
The helmet was blocking--
头盔屏蔽了...
Oh, no. Krel, it's not him! I was wrong!
不  克雷尔  不是他  我弄错了
He is an idiot!
他只是个笨蛋
It seems there's been a misunderstanding here.
看起来这里有些误会
My apologies. You are just an idiot!
对不起  你只是个笨蛋
Oh, yeah? Well, my fist is gonna misunderstand your face.
是吗  我的拳头和你的脸也有误会
Krel! Rule number three!
克雷尔  第三条法则
Lights out, plebe.
你完了  垃圾
Dude!
哥们
I'm-- I'm leaking fluid. What is this?
我在漏液体  这是什么
I must be dying. Is this the end?
我肯定死了  就这样结束了吗
Not yet.
还没有
Get away from my little brother,snack butt.\
别碰我的小弟  臭小子